







Summary

Jump to Section

A Bachelor of Technology graduate with majors in Computer & Science and having 4.4 years of qualitative and rich professional experience in ServiceNow.

Work Experience | Education | IT Skills | Projects |

currently working as Sr. ServiceNow Developer (Associate Consultant) with Infosys Technology and the area of expertise includes ServiceNow, Html, CSS and JavaScript.

Configured Applications using Service-Now tool used in ITIL Management. Strong understanding of ITIL V3. Deep functional and technical knowledge of the ServiceNow platform as well as experience delivering medium to large-scale Service Now implementations.

In-depth knowledge of the technical implementation of Change Management, Incident Management, Problem Management, Service Catalog, Configuration Management, Reporting and Integrations.

Good knowledge of ITIL processes and standards which are helpful in development, customization of the ITSM,ITBM applications, Integration with third party tool and Service Portal.

Work Experience

Infosys Limited as Senior Associate Consultant Apr 2019 to Till Date

Senior Servicenow developer

• Accenture Solutions Pvt. Ltd. as Cloud Migration & Imp Delivery Analyst Sep 2016 to Apr 2019

^ Back to Top

Education

UG: B.Tech/B.E. (Computers) from West Bengal University of Technology (WBUT) in 2016

^ Back to Top

IT Skills

Skill Name	Version	Last Used	Experience
ITIL, ServiceNOW	Orlando	2020	4 Year(s)
JavaScript. HTML5. CSS		2020	4 Year(s)

1

Important

 Using Free CV Search you have access to featured candidate profiles of Naukri. You can browse through the profiles and email the candidates of your choice directly using the email option provided. To prevent misuse of candidate information, contact details and attached resume of the candidates have been withheld

		\-/
MySQL	2020	4 Year(s)
Windows 7 and above	2020	4 Year(s)
Geneva & Version	2020	4 Year(s)
AGILE	2020	4 Year(s)

^ Back to Top

Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
ENGLISH				
HINDI				

^ Back to Top

Projects

Project Title: MacDonalds

Client: McDonalds

Nature of Employment: Full Time Project Location: Bangalore Role: Sr. Programmer Duration: Apr 2019 - Dec 2020 Onsite / Offsite: Offsite Team Size: 7

Skill Used: Servicenow, Integration, Javascript, Ajax, JSON, Rest,

Role Description: Senior ServiceNow Developer

Project Details: McDonalds is now operating a single, standardized Service Portal that scales to meet the demands of their global footprint, provides an intuitive interface that works on any device, and allows code-free customization to address local needs quickly. As the global scope grows and changes, all modifications and changes can be made inhouse with standardized OOB ServiceNow functionality.

^ Back to Top

Affirmative Action

Work Authorization

Category: General Job Type: Permanent
Physically Challenged: No Employment Status: Full time

^ Back to Top

Careers - About Us - Clients - Terms & Conditions - FAQ's - Contact Us - Report a Problem - Site Map - Resources
Our Partners: Jeevansathi Matrimonials - ICICIcommunities.org - 99acres - Real Estate In India
All rights reserved © 2021 Info Edge India Ltd.

Careers - About Us - Clients - Terms & Conditions - FAQs - Contact Us - Report a Problem - Site Map - Resources
Our Partners: Jeevansathi Matrimonials - ICICIcommunities.org - 99acres - Real Estate In India
All rights reserved © 2021 Info Edge India Ltd.